goodservice.in 2015-07-02

# Good service - get anything done over chat

## Privacy Policy

The Company ("Goodservice") recognizes that its customers, visitors and users, want to know where and how will the information they submit be used. The Company (hereinafter “Goodservice” / “We”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of the Goodservice software application (the “Application”) and [www.goodservice.in](http://www.goodservice.in/ "www.goodservice.in") (the “Site”) about our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information (“Personally Identifiable Information”) defined below. 

The Application is intended for people who are competent to contract under applicable law. Individuals who are less than 18 years old are not permitted to use this application unless the complete Agreement is seen and agreed by parents or their legal guardians under applicable law. You confirm that You are at least 18 year old or otherwise competent to contract including with consent of Your parent/legal guardian as may be required under applicable law.

This Policy is part of our Terms of Service and applies to the Personally Identifiable Information that is collected in connection with the download, installation and use of the Application and related services. By using the Application or the Site You signify Your assent to this Privacy Policy and consent to the processing of Your Personally Identifiable Information as described herein. If You do not agree with this Policy, or with our Terms of Service, do not download, install and / or use the Application

### 1\. Information Collection

"Personally Identifiable Information" means any information that either on its own or when combined with certain other information can identify an individual and for the purpose of this Privacy Policy usually limited to Your mobile phone number or address.

Goodservice may obtain the following types of information from or concerning You or Your mobile device, which may include personal information that can be used to identify You as specified below:

#### User Provided Information:

You provide certain Personally Identifiable Information, such as Your mobile phone number, name and mobile device information to Goodservice when choosing to participate in the use of the Goodservice application, such as registering as a user, messaging Goodservice, uploading images. In order to provide the Goodservice service, Goodservice shall periodically access Your location on Your mobile phone to to ensure a better user experience.

#### Cookies Information:

When you visit the Goodservice Site, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Goodservice uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, the Goodservice Site may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

Log File Information: When you use the Goodservice Site or Application, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser or application sends. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser, your phone number, and various status information. When you use the Goodservice application, our servers log certain general information that our application sends whenever a message is sent or received, error information, including time and date stamps of messages sent and received.

Goodservice may receive data whenever You connect with an application or site through Goodservice (such as when you visit an external link from Goodservice). This may include date and time You visit the site, the web address and IP address information.

If the recipient can be messaged via the Goodservice application, the message is delivered to that recipient via data service routed through our servers. Any messages that are undelivered are held on the Goodservice servers until they can be delivered or for a period of 30 days whichever is earlier.

Goodservice may retain date and time stamp information associated with successfully delivered messages as well as any other information that Goodservice is legally compelled to collect in accordance with retention policies applicable under Indian law.

### 2\. Use of Information

We neither share nor sell without Your consent Your Personally Identifiable Information such as Your mobile phone number and address book and any other information we may collect with any third parties for use for commercial, advertising and or similar marketing purposes without Your consent. However, in the future as apart of a specific promotion or feature You may specifically choose to opt-in/opt-out for any specific product and or service which may allow Your personal information to be used for such purposes.

We may share Your Personally Identifiable Information and Contents to deliver the services desired by You to the extent it is necessary to maintain or further develop and enhance our Application and to ensure the functionality and security of our services and to prevent and investigate any fraud and other misuse.

We may share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, asset views, number of clicks, etc.) with third-parties to better understand usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality related to Goodservice application.

We may use cookies and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you use the WhatsApp Service or WhatsApp Site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor individual and aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (d) track your entries, submissions, views and such.

We may disclose the Personally Identifiable Information and available user Contents as required pursuant to applicable laws, a directive or order of a government entity or statutory authority or any judicial or regulatory authority or to law enforcement agencies in any official investigation including but not limited to cyber incidents, prosecution and punishment of offences. You agree that Goodservice has the right to monitor the Application electronically from time to time and to disclose information as may be necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or other governmental request, to operate the Application properly for justified purposes that are relevant for the features and functionalities of the Application and related services opted by You, or to protect itself or its subscribers. We may transfer Your Personally Identifiable Information or other information collected, stored, processed by Goodservice to any other entity or organization located in India or outside India only in case it is necessary for providing services to You in connection with Application. Except with Your consent including under this Agreement for specified purposes, We will not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information to any third party. We will cooperate with the appropriate law enforcement authorities in investigating claims of illegal activity.

You may chose not to submit Personally Identifiable Information through Goodservice application in which case we may not be able to provide You part or full services in connection with the application. If You do not agree with any of the Terms including our Privacy Policy, You may delete Your account or not access download and use the Application. Upon deletion of Your account, Your Personally Identifiable Information and any associated Contents, except to the extent required to be retained under applicable law, will be deleted from our servers.

In the interest of protecting Your privacy and for security measures, Goodservice ensures to take reasonable steps to identify and authorise You before registering Your mobile phone number and granting You use of the Goodservice application.

### 3\. Security of Personal Information

We have implemented commercially reasonable physical, managerial, operational and technical security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration and to preserve the security of the Personally Identifiable Information in our care. Our security practices and procedures limit access to personal information on need to know basis only.

Such measures may include, where appropriate, the use of firewalls, secure server facilities, implementing proper access rights management systems and processes, careful selection of processors, standard authentication and encryption policies for our servers and other technically and commercially reasonable measures.

However, Goodservice cannot guarantee in any way with respect to any Personally Identifiable Information or Contents that You upload transmit, share or display through the Application or the Site and You do so at Your own risk.

Using unsecured or other unprotected networks to send messages and use of other features through the Goodservice application is not recommended.

If Goodservice learns of a security breach, then we may attempt to notify You electronically so that You can take appropriate protective steps. 

### 4\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

Any changes in the Privacy Policy by Goodservice shall be posted on our website [www.goodservice.in](http://www.goodservice.in/ "www.goodservice.in") to reflect changes in our policy so that the users are always aware of what information we collect, use, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose it. Users should periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Once posted, those changes are effective immediately. Continued access or use of the Application constitutes Your acceptance of the changes and the amended Policy.
